



I am a student with a good knowledge and understanding of creating websites. My experience has led me to carry out some paid freelance work. I am very determined to develop further. I learn new things very quickly. The experience of attending school and working part-time since the age of 18 has led me to manage my time very well. My passion aside from IT is travelling, which is one of the reasons why I decided to study abroad. The experience I have gained from travelling to new countries has led me to adapt to new conditions and situations very quickly.

EXPERIENCE

November 2020 - Present

Kitchen Assistant/Waiter, Dragonfly Bistro, Aberystwyth, UK

Dragonfly Bistro is small vegan/vegetarian restaurant in Aberystwyth with a 5 star hygiene rating.

- I provide excellent customer service which is reflected from the feedback from both my managers and customers
- I always go above and beyond in promoting selected items to help achieve the company's goal of reducing waste
- Preparing food under time pressure with the highest standards of hygiene
- A good understanding of the importance of cross contamination and handling of food with allergens

January 2021 - April 2021

Freelancer, Poland

I teamed up with a friend to work on some paid freelance projects

- Collected information from clients to gather what was needed for the project and made the initial graphic design for the website
- Created the website code (HTML / CSS / JS) based on the graphic project
- Negotiated financial terms with clients
- We sold five project which included websites, form and logos to name a few

June 2019 - October 2019

Sales Representative, 24 IT, Poland

24 IT is a telecommunications company that mainly sells fibre optic internet

- Came up with promotions for the company and presented it to new customers
- Arranged meetings with clients and colleagues to present work progress

July 2018 - August 2020

Kitchen Assistant/Waiter, Poland

- As this was my first job, I had to learn a lot of different skills to work as a kitchen assistance and waiter
- When serving customers I always did this to the highest standard, being friendly, approachable and speedy

EDUCATION

SEPTEMBER 2020 - PRESENT

Business Information Technology (with integrated year in industry)

Introduction to Programming (C)

Create a simple Arduino program using loops, conditional statements, arrays and structures

• Functional Programming (Haskell)

Introduction to the HASKELL functional language. Writing simple programs.

• Fundamentals of Web Development (HTML, CSS, JS)

Acquainting with the basics of creating websites (HTML, CSS, JS). Focus on presenting HTML5 standards.

• Programming Using an Object-Oriented Language (Java)

Introduction to object-oriented programming. The main task was to write a Java object-oriented quiz game program.

• Programming for the Web (PHP SQL)

Introduction to SQL and PHP. The main assignment was the creation of a website with a login and registration system and games in JS.

Software Engineering for the Web (10 week group project)

Learning to work in a group. As a team leader, I was responsible for creating our work plan. Helping others when they encountered a problem or had a problem with making it on time. I also created documentation and wrote HTML and CSS code.

SKILLS

- HTML/CSS
- SASS
- JS
- GitHub
- Bootstrap

LANGUAGES

• Polish - native

• English - advanced

INTERESTS

- Travelling
- Psychology

- Economy
- Sports